

My Contact

nikoblue12@gmail.com



+62822-5343-2205



https://www.instagram.com/nnxikoo/



https://www.linkedin.com/in/nikolausriosaputra/



Jl. Tj. Gedong 1 No.46, RT.5/RW.16 Tomang, Kec.Grogol Petamburan, Kota Jakarta Barat

Hard Skill

- HTML
- CSS
- JAVASCRIPT
- PYTHON
- C++
- MICROSOFT OFFICE
- FIGMA

Soft Skill

- Observation
- Decision making
- Communication
- Multi-tasking
- Solve Problem
- Work in Team
- Time management
- Hard working
- Ability work under pressure

Education Background

(2021-Present)

TARUMANAGARA UNIVERSITY

Faculty of Information Technology GPA: 3.53

FRANSISKUS ASSISI SENIOR HIGH SCHOOL

(2016-2019)

Natural Science Student High School Student Council (2017-2018) Sports Section Coordinator (2017-2018)

NIKOLAUS RIO SAPUTRA

INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY STUDENT

About Me

Hello, I am an Information Technology student. I'm currently digging in front-end and back-end services. Also, I learn new things every day even though there is little information I gather but I want to learn and continue to develop myself and gain experience.



Experience

Feb 2022 - Mar 2022

JNT. - Freelance Admin warehouse

Key responsibilities:

• input data, report, and evaluate everything related to the entry and exit of goods in the warehouse

Feb 2022 - Mar 2022

Sport Olympiad President University. - Logistic

Key responsibilities:

Successfully organize logistic in the biggest event in president university

Nov 11 - 13th 2022

Fun Hiking. - Tarumanagara University

Key responsibilities:

• Climbing Mount Gede Pangrango with Mapala FTI

<u>Training/Bootcamp</u>

Ifabula.-Reactive Web Development With Outsystems

Sep 2022 - Oct 2022

 Using low code to make web apps more responsive, flexible with Outsystem Bootcamp

Dicoding Academy. -Cloudeka Digischool

Sep 2022 - Oct 2022

- Learn Basic Web Programming : The total hours needed to complete this class is 55 hours with average class exam score 100% and the final project gets a score 4 to 5
- Learn JavaScript Programming Basics: The total hours needed to complete this class is 45 hours, with average class exam score 100%

Digital Codepolitan.

Oct 2022 - Nov 2022

• Learn Python Basics : learn basic python with a total study time of 3 hours and make a small project contact management

Achievements

Nov 3-4th 2018

Ist place in the Big Champion of Kushin

Ryu Karate Championship

March 2-4th 2018 3rd place in the East Kalimantan

Karate Championship

March 26th 2021 Ist place in the KMK CUP PUBG

tournament